<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto Dictionary</title>
    <link>https://cryptodictionary.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Crypto Dictionary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://cryptodictionary.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Book</title>
      <link>https://cryptodictionary.github.io/thebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cryptodictionary.github.io/thebook/</guid>
      <description>Crypto Dictionary is rigorous in its definitions, yet easy to read and laced with humor. Flip to any random page to discover something new or mind-boggling, from history trivia to the lastest research concepts.
Crypto Dictionary is available as a DRM-free e-book and soon as printed copy via No Starch Press. It will also be available on the all major book resellers, including Amazon, B&amp;amp;N, Penguin.
Get a free sample chapter including the &amp;ldquo;B&amp;rdquo; definitions, including for example:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Author</title>
      <link>https://cryptodictionary.github.io/theauthor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cryptodictionary.github.io/theauthor/</guid>
      <description>Jean-Philippe (JP) Aumasson is the Chief Security Officer and cofounder of Taurus Group, a Swiss financial tech company specializing in digital assets infrastructure. As part of this role, he co-designed the leading custody solution for blockchain-based assets used by Swiss financial institutions.
The author of the acclaimed book Serious Cryptography (No Starch Press, 2017), he speaks regularly at information security and technology conferences.
JP obtained a PhD from EPFL and worked in the Kudelski Group for 10 years, where held various responsibilities from pay-TV cryptography engineering, security consulting for the private and public sector, technologist, source code auditor, and security researcher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra Content</title>
      <link>https://cryptodictionary.github.io/extracontent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cryptodictionary.github.io/extracontent/</guid>
      <description>The new definitions on this page extend those already in Crypto Dictionary, and might appear in future versions of the book.
This is work in progress. New definitions will appear regularly.
(For their help, thanks to: Antony Vennard.)
0 ePrint crasher.
Online:
 https://eprint.iacr.org/2021/323  אתבש Like Noekeon and ROT13, an involution. About as secure as the latter. Pronounced &amp;ldquo;atbash&amp;rdquo;.
API Cryptographic APIs have often been confusing and error-prone for cryptographers, and impenetrable for mere mortals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
